{"479050310.432638": {
"front": "479050525.977355",
"right": "null",
"back": "null",
"left": "null"
},
"479050525.977355":{
"front":"479050707.923526",
"right": "479050479.215060",
"back":"479050310.432638",
"left": "null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479050479.215060":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"null",
"left":"479050525.977355",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479050707.923526":{
"front":"479050790.182485",
"right":"null",
"back":"479050525.977355",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479050790.182485":{
"front":"479050828.104607",
"right":"null",
"back":"479050707.923526",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479050828.104607":{
"front":"479051191.535574",
"right":"null",
"back":"479050790.182485",
"left":"479051094.371416",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051094.371416":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479050828.104607",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051191.535574":{
"front":"479051321.268617",
"right":"null",
"back":"479050828.104607",
"left":"479051269.405020",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051269.405020":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479051191.535574",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051321.268617":{
"front":"479051507.689572",
"right":"null",
"back":"479051191.535574",
"left":"479051454.311288",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479051454.311288":{
"front":"479051399.292662",
"right":"479051321.268617",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051399.292662":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"479051454.311288",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051507.689572":{
"front":"479052861.039248",
"right":"null",
"back":"479051321.268617",
"left":"479051553.401475",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479051553.401475":{
"front":"479052265.379253",
"right":"479051507.689572",
"back":"null",
"left":"479051601.769144",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051601.769144":{
"front":"479052151.846866",
"right":"479051553.401475",
"back":"479051657.911083",
"left":"479052100.836295",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479051657.911083":{
"front":"479051601.769144",
"right":"479052041.434693",
"back":"null",
"left":"479051916.597958",
"rotate": "90"
},
"479051916.597958":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479051657.911083",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479052041.434693":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"null",
"left":"479051657.911083",
"rotate": "180"
},
"479052100.836295":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479051601.769144",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479052151.846866":{
"front":"479052206.289059",
"right":"null",
"back":"479051601.769144",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479052206.289059":{
"front":"479053422.145996",
"right":"479053093.765910",
"back":"479052151.846866",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479052265.379253":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"479051553.401475",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479052861.039248":{
"front":"479052887.008706",
"right":"null",
"back":"479051507.689572",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479052887.008706":{
"front":"479053068.588134",
"right":"null",
"back":"479052861.039248",
"left":"479052973.368968",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479053068.588134":{
"front":"479052908.721157",
"right":"null",
"back":"479052887.008706",
"left":"479053093.765910",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479052908.721157":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"479053068.588134",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479052973.368968":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479052887.008706",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479053093.765910":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479053068.588134",
"back":"479053139.217847",
"left":"479052206.289059",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479053139.217847":{
"front":"479053093.765910",
"right":"null",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "90"
},
"479053422.145996":{
"front":"479053328.149471",
"right":"null",
"back":"479052206.289059",
"left":"479053388.668675",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479053388.668675":{
"front":"478505062.248392",
"right":"479053422.145996",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
},
"479053328.149471":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"null",
"left":"479053422.145996",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"478505062.248392":{
"front":"479053752.291663",
"right":"null",
"back":"479053388.668675",
"left":"479053620.173104",
"rotate": "90"
},
"479053620.173104":{
"front":"null",
"right":"478505062.248392",
"back":"null",
"left":"479053675.664591",
"rotate": "180"
},
"479053752.291663":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"478505062.248392",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-90"
},
"479053675.664591":{
"front":"null",
"right":"479053620.173104",
"back":"null",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "180"
},
"":{
"front":"null",
"right":"null",
"back":"",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "0"
}
}
